<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Loyagami Indonesia | Real Estate Asset &amp; Investment Management Platform</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thirdhome.space/en/feed/?simply_static_page=721" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/</link>
	<description>Makes property-based investment and asset management easier</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 04:56:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>Powered by Teleciuos?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The role of smart buildings in the development of smart cities</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/the-role-of-smart-buildings-in-the-development-of-smart-cities/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/the-role-of-smart-buildings-in-the-development-of-smart-cities/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 04:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investment and Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=4418</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
		<div id="fws_63c7b7457306c"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col no-extra-padding inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" >
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>The demand for buildings and cities to become more liveable, workable and sustainable due to the global push towards net-zero targets combined with population and urbanisation growth, forecasts that the global smart cities market will be valued at $3.6 trillion by 2025.</p>
</blockquote>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b74573491"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>Governments across the world in progressive locations from Singapore to Helsinki and Zurich, are also now developing ambitious smart city initiatives to hit their own mid-century targets, as called for by The Paris Agreement. Designated city zones known as Smart Quarters are being developed, and entire smart cities that are truly sustainable are being envisioned, with intelligent buildings, cleaner transportation and infrastructures that serve essential human needs such as security, comfort and connectivity.</p>
<p>The rapid evolution of next-generation technologies such as artificial intelligence (AI), personalised healthcare and sustainable energy generation are also key drivers of the smart cities’ future. Furthermore, with cities and their buildings currently accounting for 65% of global energy demand, it is evident that the buildings we construct today are crucial for the evolution of smart cities and our push towards net-zero targets.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b745737a9"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="nectar-animated-title" data-style="color-strip-reveal" data-color="accent-color">
	<div class="nectar-animated-title-outer">
		<div class="nectar-animated-title-inner">
			<div class="wrap"><h6 style="color: #ffffff;">Supporting buildings of the future</h6></div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>Intelligent buildings are a vital element to a future where cities become safe, smart and sustainable and building owners can harness and control their own energy usage.</p>
<p>Smart building technology has already helped many thousands of buildings and homes consume energy more efficiently. ABB has supported the construction of the New Development Bank (NDB) Headquarters in Shanghai by installing an intelligent and integrated building controls system, to manage indoor lighting, electric curtains and windows that involve more than 8,000 control circuits. Following the installation, the NBD Headquarters was able to make energy savings of more than 15% compared to conventional systems.</p>
<p>2021 marks a turning point in our collective ability to bring down emissions in our cities, save energy, and speed up the transition to renewable energy with smart buildings and power grids though the convergence of AI and IoT.</p>
<p>As emerging technologies continue to develop, more opportunities arise for buildings to leverage new technological processes and data sources. The concept of using technology to improve our cities and buildings is not a new one, but what <em>is</em> different is that IoT is now enabling us to connect an increasing number of devices which were not connected before. Connectivity really is the key to unleashing the true potential of intelligent buildings, unlocking opportunities for new information from infinite sources to be analyzed and combined, offering a new level of intelligence.</p>
<p>However, it is not just about using new technologies; smart thinking and the optimisation of existing buildings is a key factor when it comes to accelerating the sustainable development of smart cities globally. ABB is working closely with cities and utilities to obtain greater efficiencies from existing infrastructure and build unified, attractive city services as part of a move towards smarter cities. With IoT technologies, older buildings can take full advantage of the data they generate and adjust to how they operate.</p>
<p>One city doing just that is Zaragoza, the capital of Aragon, Spain. The city sought to reduce its total energy consumption by 20% with a focus on four major Zaragoza smart city buildings: the historical Seminario of Zaragoza, which houses City Hall offices, the main City Hall, the main police station and the Technology &amp; Art Center. Advanced energy monitoring was provided through a cloud-based energy management platform to bring the four buildings into compliance with the ISO 50001 standard. As a consequence, Zaragoza was able to fulfill the first steps on its way to compliance, and the collaboration resulted in savings of up to 30% in operational costs.</p>
<p>Another great example of smart city technology in action can be found in Hanoi, Vietnam. As part of the project, Vietnamese multinational telecommunication service, Viettel Group, is targetting to achieve their green objectives. Viettel wanted their headquarters in Hanoi to be a symbol of innovation and to set the standard for the rest of their buildings around the world. In order to meet the high demand for safe, smart and connected workplaces, a range of smart building technology has been supplied. Key to the project was the <em>i-bus KNX system</em>, with all devices of the building ranging from lighting and shutter control to heating, ventilation, security and energy management communicating with one and another via a single bus interface.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b74573c9b"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="nectar-animated-title" data-style="color-strip-reveal" data-color="accent-color">
	<div class="nectar-animated-title-outer">
		<div class="nectar-animated-title-inner">
			<div class="wrap"><h6 style="color: #ffffff;">Turning existing infrastructure into smart buildings for smart cities</h6></div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>So, what are the challenges when it comes to upgrading existing building infrastructure, and how can smart, IoT-based technology overcome them?</p>
	</div>
</div>



<div class="nectar-fancy-ul" data-list-icon="icon-salient-thin-line" data-animation="false" data-animation-delay="0" data-color="accent-color" data-spacing="default" data-alignment="left"> 
<ul>
<li><strong>Financing:</strong> Upgrading a building may seem like a costly expense, however the advancements in IoT mean this is no longer the case.  Modern sensors can be connected wirelessly, without the need for expensive installation costs. The reduced energy and maintenance costs allow for a quick return on investment, with figures showing that intelligent buildings use 20-40% less energy and result in 8 – 9% lower operating expenses than those with older systems.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Maintenance: </strong>Predictive fault-finding can save maintenance time and labor, as well as minimising downtime for expensive equipment or services. Some estimates suggest that smart-enabled predictive maintenance is three to nine times cheaper than a traditional reactive approach. Tenant and occupant satisfaction are often also higher as systems that experience failure can be identified, repaired and re-booted quickly.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><strong>Design: </strong>Older buildings may not have been designed with smart technology in mind, but the latest technology is usually compact and lightweight, from IP entry systems to light switches through to energy management systems, making them easy to fit even the hardest to reach places. Wireless sensors are discreet and have an adhesive backing which can simply be stuck to walls, desks or ceilings with no screwing or external fixings required. Thick walls, which can sometimes obscure wi-fi signals, can be overcome with the use of ‘repeaters’ or signal-boosters, which help to extend the range of the products.</li>
</ul>
 </div>
			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b7457401b"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="nectar-animated-title" data-style="color-strip-reveal" data-color="accent-color">
	<div class="nectar-animated-title-outer">
		<div class="nectar-animated-title-inner">
			<div class="wrap"><h6 style="color: #ffffff;">A holistic ecosystem</h6></div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>Developing a holistic ecosystem where everything is connected and interoperable should be the key aim when it comes to smart city buildings now and in the future, from safety and security to comfort and control. Linking all elements of the smart building together into one easy-to-use system, that ultimately drives energy efficiency and reduces operating costs, from door entry to emergency lighting to harnessing the power of the sun through solar and integrating this with E-mobility solutions, such as EV charging.</p>
<p>A combination of solar power, smart energy management and a highly efficient cogeneration plant have proven to deliver enough energy to power a whole factory and save huge amounts of CO2 at ABB’s Busch-Jaeger subsidiary in Lüdenscheid. The carbon neutral factory generated 1,100 MWh in its first year, which was enough climate-neutral power to cover 100% of the factory’s power requirements on sunny days. It has also reduced the site’s CO2e emissions by some 680 tons per year.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b7457435e"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="nectar-animated-title" data-style="color-strip-reveal" data-color="accent-color">
	<div class="nectar-animated-title-outer">
		<div class="nectar-animated-title-inner">
			<div class="wrap"><h6 style="color: #ffffff;">The future is now</h6></div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>From home and office to transport and utilities, 2021 is the year that smart cities will begin to take shape. Advances in IoT and AI will bring together smart buildings, smart power grids, and EV charging to form a new smart society ecosystem that is increasingly interconnected and efficient, helping us to live comfortably and securely, while protecting our planet for future generations.</p>
<p>What is clear is that our focus should not be limited to smart cities. It is important that we also take into consideration the crucial role that smart industry, regional infrastructure and settlements play in building the societies of today and of the future. Keeping us safe and secure is a major element on our journey to creating smart cities that are in tune with the needs of current and future generations.c</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/the-role-of-smart-buildings-in-the-development-of-smart-cities/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indonesian Millennials Put Homeownership Last on bucket list</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/residential/indonesian-millennials-put-homeownership-last-on-bucket-list/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/residential/indonesian-millennials-put-homeownership-last-on-bucket-list/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 01:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Residential]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=4377</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
		<div id="fws_63c7b74576184"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col no-extra-padding inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" >
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<blockquote class="wp-block-quote">
<p>“I’ve been working for 16 years now and, to have a house, it seems difficult and impossible with my current situation,” said Bunga, 37, who lives in Lenteng Agung, South Jakarta.</p>
<p><cite>Bunga Pertiwi Adek Puteri</cite></p>
</blockquote>
<p> </p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b7457645d"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>As an office worker with one daughter, Kiandra Anaia, 5, Bunga admitted that the increasing house prices in Jakarta were the primary reason why she decided to put her dream of having a house on hold – perhaps forever. Bunga described herself as part of the “sandwich generation” who became the backbone of her family – at least five people depend on her. Neither of her parents have retirement funds, so Bunga needs to take care of them. Her younger sister also has a 6-year-old daughter who is about to enter elementary school. They all live in Bunga’s mother’s house.</p>
<p>“My salary is divided between the six of us […] so what I’m doing right now is focusing on the current needs and the education of the kids,” said Bunga, who also has a small business selling lemonade. Bunga recently separated from her husband and did not receive alimony – a situation that further exacerbated any plans to purchase her own house.</p>
<p>For Bunga, even saving money for a down payment to buy either a house or an apartment is difficult – especially if the property in question is in Jakarta. In 2019, the World Bank published a report that cited evidence suggesting that house price-to-income ratios in Jakarta were higher than in New York.</p>
<p>The report quoted calculations made by Statistics Indonesia (BPS) that showed Jakarta’s house price-to-income ratio to be 10.3, while those of Denpasar, Bali and Bandung, West Java were 12.1 and 11.9 respectively. Data from Demographia and Nomura showed that those numbers were double the house price-to-income ratios in New York and Singapore.</p>
<p>“[But] if I buy a [cheaper] house outside Jakarta, it will cost me more in the future – from transportation to my parents’ needs,” she said. “So purchasing a house can wait until later. Right now, the most important thing is daily needs, having life insurance and saving up for the kids’ education,” said Bunga, adding that she could rely on her office for health insurance. Bunga said she viewed other Indonesians who were not part of the “sandwich generation” as luckier because they could just focus on themselves or perhaps their children.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b74576765"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>Ria, 29, who lives in Yogyakarta, is single with no children and probably not part of the “sandwich generation” that Bunga mentioned. However, having a house does not cross Ria’s mind at the moment.</p>
<p>“Perhaps, I will think about it when I’m 33,” said Ria, who works at an international organization. As a single woman, Ria finds it a little awkward when looking for a property in Indonesia. She recalled her experience with a property agent and the first question from his mouth was whether she was married or not. “Instead of asking me where I’m working,” she quipped.</p>
<p>As a result, Ria decided to spoil herself a little bit by traveling or buying assets such as gold or stocks, where her marital status would never be a problem.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b74576b09"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="nectar-animated-title" data-style="color-strip-reveal" data-color="accent-color">
	<div class="nectar-animated-title-outer">
		<div class="nectar-animated-title-inner">
			<div class="wrap"><h6 style="color: #ffffff;">Home Financing &amp; Mortagage</h6></div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p dir="ltr">Marine Novita, the CEO of Rumah.com, a website that offers houses for sale or rent, admitted that based on her company’s survey of 1,000 people including millennials, the mortgage process was still complicated.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“The paperwork tends to be complicated. We at Rumah.com can assist until the process to the bank. We also work together with one of the banks in the hope that this will ease the process of applying for a mortgage. But, of course, the bank needs to be reminded so they can respond quickly. Sometimes a customer applies today, but the response comes a few days later,” she said.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Andra Matin, an architect, acknowledged that while he already worked hard to provide budget housing with an emphasis on aesthetics, he still saw many millennials struggled to purchase a house.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b74576e32"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col padding-2-percent inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-border-radius="5px" data-shadow="small_depth" data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" ><div class="column-bg-overlay-wrap column-bg-layer" data-bg-animation="none"><div class="column-bg-overlay"></div></div>
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="nectar-animated-title" data-style="color-strip-reveal" data-color="accent-color">
	<div class="nectar-animated-title-outer">
		<div class="nectar-animated-title-inner">
			<div class="wrap"><h6 style="color: #ffffff;">Complicated &amp; Unpleasant Home Buying Experience</h6></div>
		</div>
	</div>
</div>
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p dir="ltr">Erik Sofiatry, 35, a lecturer and a researcher, got his house in Sumbawa, West Nusa Tenggara in October 2020 for Rp 240 million ($16,484). He said the nitty-gritty of the administrative work in purchasing a house would turn off many millennials.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“I got the house because my developer was smart in seeking a way to fulfill the document that is impossible for me to provide,” said Erik.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Erik described the administrative requirements of purchasing a house as “too complicated.” He highlighted the lack of using a single data source, like E-KTP, as the problem. He recalled that he was required to provide several letters from his subdistrict stating that he was, indeed, a resident of that subdistrict.</p>
<p dir="ltr"> “I thought the point of having an E-KTP [integrated data] is to be able to be mobile without that administrative &#8220;border&#8221; within my country,” said Erik.</p>
<p dir="ltr">In addition, Erik said that both the down payment and later installments in purchasing a house were too expensive for commercial housing.</p>
<p dir="ltr">“The mortgage requires you to have multiple guarantees from work, approval from your supervisors, etc. What if you are not working long-term with the company? They would not approve it. I think it also requires a letter of approval from your spouse. If you are single and marriage is not on your map, then you are done!” he said.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/residential/indonesian-millennials-put-homeownership-last-on-bucket-list/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When and Why You Need of Fund Raise Solution</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/when-and-why-you-need-of-fund-raise-solution/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/when-and-why-you-need-of-fund-raise-solution/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 11:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investment and Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3965</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Short explanation when and why you need our solution to raise funds safely, precisely, quickly and with measurable risks]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Simple explanation when and why you need our solution to raise funds safely, precisely, quickly and with measurable risks</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/when-and-why-you-need-of-fund-raise-solution/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fixed Asset Valuation Method &#8211; Ep 1</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/fixed-asset-valuation-method-ep-1/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 08:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investment and Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3931</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Valuation method for purchasing home or commercial assets - Indonesian]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[Valuation method for purchasing home or commercial assets - Indonesian]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Macro Factors in Assessing Business &#038; Investment Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/macro-factors-in-assessing-business-investment-plans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 03:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investment and Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3912</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Factors that become our assessment factors in analyzing real estate-based businesses - in Bahasa Indonesia]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Macro Factors in Assessing Business &amp; Investment Plans</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Buy Property Like Professional Property Investor</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/how-to-make-money-as-a-professional-property-investor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 02:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investment and Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/investment-and-finance/how-to-make-money-as-a-professional-property-investor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There’s something that seems to be common to lots of Indonesians — we love to own property]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div id="fws_63c7b7457bbc4"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col no-extra-padding inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" >
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>There is something that seems common to many Indonesians &#8211; namely, the joy of owning property. Of course, this is made more difficult because most of us want to live near the business area (CBD) of a big city, near the beach, or close to other great amenities that make work and non-work life enjoyable.</p>
<p>One of the perhaps slightly positive impacts of the Coronavirus tragedy is the trend of working from home, which is sure to see more company leaders encourage their staff to work productively from home.</p>
<p>This will increase the demand for property in the outer suburbs that may be one to two hours from a major city or business and work center.</p>
<p>At this time of the pandemic, many CBD apartments that were once easy to rent out for tourists or foreign workers and students have become difficult to rent for the long term and some investors / property owners have even decided to sell them. This means that some apartments that may have been too expensive for young people to buy in the days before the pandemic are now more affordable, especially if they are bought for rent.</p>
<p>Many first-time homebuyers, unable to buy property in the city where they want to live, can actually buy a house and rent it out until they can afford to live on the property they purchased. By doing so, you can benefit from the tax deductions that make the buy-for-rent deal successful.</p>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b7457bf4a"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col no-extra-padding inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" >
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				<div class="nectar-fancy-ul" data-list-icon="icon-salient-thin-line" data-animation="false" data-animation-delay="0" data-color="accent-color" data-spacing="default" data-alignment="left"> If you’re thinking about becoming a landlord/property investor, then here are some questions, we suggest you should answer these questions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Do you really understand how the investment works and structure? This includes the tax benefits and how you’ll make the payments.</li>
<li>What is the business case for the investment? Would the average person buy this property? Do you know what it will actually cost you? How much will you make if you keep the investment for five or 10 years?</li>
<li>Does it commercially make sense? Is this the best use of your money? Could you buy cheaper, better and with more potential capital gain?</li>
<li>What could go wrong? Are you able to pivot if interest rates change or a tenant doesn’t pay your rent, etc?</li>
<li>Can you easily obtain the due diligence on the investment and people engaged in it? Do you have the lawyers/experts to make sure you don’t buy into a bad investment? Remember those who bought into apartments with cracks in the walls and fire-threatening panelling!</li>
<li>Will my investment withstand an unexpected economic shock or event? How would your investment deal with another pandemic?</li>
</ul>
<p> </div>
			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
		<div id="fws_63c7b7457c150"  data-column-margin="default" data-midnight="dark"  class="wpb_row vc_row-fluid vc_row"  style="padding-top: 0px; padding-bottom: 0px; "><div class="row-bg-wrap" data-bg-animation="none" data-bg-animation-delay="" data-bg-overlay="false"><div class="inner-wrap row-bg-layer" ><div class="row-bg viewport-desktop"  style=""></div></div></div><div class="row_col_wrap_12 col span_12 dark left">
	<div  class="vc_col-sm-12 wpb_column column_container vc_column_container col no-extra-padding inherit_tablet inherit_phone "  data-padding-pos="all" data-has-bg-color="false" data-bg-color="" data-bg-opacity="1" data-animation="" data-delay="0" >
		<div class="vc_column-inner" >
			<div class="wpb_wrapper">
				
<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
	<div class="wpb_wrapper">
		<p>When it comes to big investments involving borrowed funds, we argue that you need to treat the investment like a new business.</p>
<p>These questions help you create a business or property investing plan. Don’t buy property without one!</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<hr />
<h4>About Loyagami</h4>
<h6>Loyagami is a real estate services company that manage individual or institutional asset to make ensure the value growing and the risk mitigated for long term</h6>
	</div>
</div>




			</div> 
		</div>
	</div> 
</div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Residential Business Opportunities for the Elderly</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/investment-and-finance/residential-business-opportunities-for-the-elderly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 01:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Investment and Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=2807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The residential market for the elderly is an opportunity and opportunities that can be glimpsed by developers in the country. In 2025 the number of elderly people (elderly) is estimated...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>The residential market for the elderly is an opportunity and opportunities that can be glimpsed by developers in the country.</p></blockquote>



<p>In 2025 the number of elderly people (elderly) is estimated to have reached 20% of the total population of Indonesia. In fact, according to the Central Statistics Agency (BPS) in 2014 the number of elderly people in Indonesia reached 20.24 million people, or the equivalent of 8.03 percent of the total population in that year.</p>



<p>Still from this data, it is stated that around 42.32 percent of the elderly live together with three generations in one household. As many as 26.80 percent of other elderly people live with the nuclear family. Meanwhile, 17.48 percent lived only with their partner. Meanwhile, the remaining 9.66 percent of the elderly live alone and have to independently meet their food, health and social needs.</p>



<p>Elderly housing are opportunities that can be looked at by developers in the country. Because although only about 8 percent, this number is equivalent to the population of Singapore and Japan.</p>



<p>In the midst of unfavorable property market conditions, there are actually many other opportunities that can be targeted by developers. One of them is housing for the elderly, and not many have developed this subsector</p>



<p>This opportunity is also in line with the government&#8217;s plan to develop 10 new Bali. And furthermore, the government only needs to add health infrastructure and if successful, of course not only Indonesians will be interested but also elderly people from abroad.</p>



<p>&#8220;Indonesia also has many urbanites who certainly rarely meet their parents, even though our parents need someone to talk to,&#8221; said an expert in the field of elderly people in Indonesia.</p>



<p>Currently, the market share for the elderly is targeting the upper middle class. However, it is also possible for the middle class or even low-income people.</p>



<p>The areas of Bandung and Bogor are potential locations for elderly nursing home developers considering their location which is not too far from Jakarta. In addition to other areas in a number of regions in Indonesia, both based on mountains and oceans, such as Bali, Malang, Yogyakarta, and other areas whose infrastructure is sufficiently good with the availability of health facilities</p>



<p>Currently, Singapore and Australia are two countries that are intensively developing special housing for the elderly.</p>



<p>Currently, countries that have taken advantage of the residential market for the elderly are Malaysia, Singapore and the Philippines. These neighboring countries attract the elderly to come and live there, including from Indonesia.</p>



<p>There are also quite a lot of business opportunities for companion or expansion of business opportunities from providing housing for the elderly, including providing facilities for the elderly for creative activities such as painting and handicrafts as well as a senior botanic garden for growing fruit, flowers and herbs.</p>



<p>This provided activity place can be intended for the elderly as end users or as a means for the elderly to provide or sell services to the public using the facilities provided</p>



<p>We open opportunities for those of you who are interested in this business to find financing partners, land owners or operations</p>



<p>Please contact us if you are interested in this business opportunity and have at least one of the advantages whether you have land and want to find partners, or are looking for partners who have land locations</p>



<div class="is-layout-flex wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-white-color has-vivid-red-background-color has-text-color has-background" style="border-radius:8px" rel="Residential Business Opportunities for the Elderly">Talk With Us</a></div>
</div>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Importance of Advances for Purchases of 20% of the Selling Price or More</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/residential/the-importance-of-advances-for-purchases-of-20-of-the-selling-price-or-more/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 15:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Residential]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=2739</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are many challenges that arise when we want to start buying housing using bank financing. According to the survey, consumers say the number one barrier to buying a house is sufficient savings or funds to pay a down payment. ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Nearly 70% of mortgage borrowers defaulted after year 3 and lost the value of their paid investment</p></blockquote>



<p></p>



<p>There are many challenges that arise when we want to start buying housing using bank financing. According to the survey, consumers say the number one barrier to buying a house is sufficient savings or funds to pay a down payment. What exactly is a down payment? Down payment is the money you spend from your own pocket to make purchases, and the next question is what is the ideal down payment for a home purchase.</p>



<p>A smart rule of thumb is to have funds available to make a down payment of at least 20 percent of the price of the house (house or apartment). This percentage value is the best standard that people often don&#8217;t know or even forget. Moreover, the promotion of 0% down payment or small down payment is very rampant, which are campaigned by both banks and property developers</p>



<p>Then why do we need to understand the importance of down payments of at least 20% of the selling price where the remaining 80% can use bank financing? The value of 20% is the minimum, and it would be even better if you provide more down payment to make a home purchase</p>



<p><strong>Reason Number 1 :</strong> <strong>Increase Opportunities to Get Bank Financing</strong></p>



<p>Basically, the banking industry will prefer buyers as debtors who have sufficient purchasing power, so that by making down payments of at least 20% or more, the chances of obtaining bank financing will be much greater than less than 20%</p>



<p><strong>Reason Number 2 :</strong> <strong>Avoid high insurance costs</strong></p>



<p>If you only pay a down payment of less than 20% of the selling price, then generally life insurance or other insurance that often debtors or buyers do not know will be greater, this is because the financing party or bank needs steps to minimize risk in case of failure. payment or other things that pose a risk to the smooth payment of the mortgage installments. So it can be said that buying a house with bank financing and a small down payment (DP) will have an impact on higher costs for those of you who must be paid in advance</p>



<p><strong>Reason Number 3 :</strong> <strong>Asset Value Is Not Commensurate With Debt Value</strong></p>



<p>If you make a purchase with a small down payment and a long term, for example 10 years or more, then the growth in the value of your assets will not be proportional to the value of your debt because the average growth in asset value per year is around 5% per year while the interest rate on debt generally 3% &#8211; 5% more expensive than the increase in property value, not to mention the decline in the value of the building which will worsen the condition if you intend to make repayments when experiencing financial problems or for the purpose of refinancing (moving financing) to another bank</p>



<p>So it can be said that when you want to sell a residence with the aim of buying a new residence when your bank debt is paid off in the 10th year or even more, then you have suffered a loss of 30% -40% of the money you spend.</p>



<p>These are the 3 main reasons why you need to review if you intend to buy a house or apartment with a down payment of less than 20%.</p>



<p>And to provide this solution, Loyagami Space provides a purchase solution through rental, where we can help potential buyers to raise money in advance without losing their dream house because it has been sold (as a strategy often used by sellers to suppress buyers) and the selling price remains the same for The next 1 or 2 years, where we buy the house we want and allow personalization through a rental scheme</p>



<p>And if you don&#8217;t get bank financing after year 1 or 2, then the price increase to buy can be negotiated so as not to burden potential buyers. This solution only applies to housing that is ready for occupancy or secondary housing</p>



<div class="is-layout-flex wp-block-buttons">
<div class="wp-block-button"><a class="wp-block-button__link has-white-color has-vivid-red-background-color has-text-color has-background" style="border-radius:5px" rel="https://www.loyagami.com/id/chat/">Talk With Us </a></div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How co-working spaces can maintain community spirit in the new normal</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/workspace/how-co-working-spaces-can-maintain-community-spirit-in-the-new-normal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/workspace/how-co-working-spaces-can-maintain-community-spirit-in-the-new-normal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Workspace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Space]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3718</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The current pandemic conditions have changed many ways of working, especially the expectations of workers to work in a co-working space]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Few things that we do to keep people engaged in shared workspace </p></blockquote>



<p>The pandemic has challenged our society and fundamentally upended its social construct. While its impact may last long with social distancing, lockdowns, and resulting economic fallout becoming the new norms, we do have the resilience to pull through these tough times.</p>



<p>Since the ease of lockdown restrictions last year, a lot of efforts have been made to ensure re-entry, return to work, and reopening of businesses and institutions. But now with the second wave of the pandemic hitting us hard, it looks all the more difficult.</p>



<p>While several industries are trying to adapt and thrive in this economic downturn there is a need for innovation, flexibility and agility in the way we operate. This has become a reality for the co-working industry in particular, as they are forced to reassess their operations, offer flexible membership plans, and introduce new business models. While adapting to accommodate the hybrid model of working and de-densifying demands of the businesses would benefit the sector in the long run, how does one ensure retention?</p>



<p>Community engagement has always been a strategy that has led to retention but it is a challenge when spaces are not allowed to bring a sizable number of people together. Here are some strategies that can assist in ensuring that you retain an engaged community despite the odds:</p>



<h3>Communicate with your community</h3>



<p>The most important thing to do is keep a consistent and open line of communication with your community at all times. Address their safety concerns by communicating the precautionary measures incorporated by your workspace. Instil a sense of confidence amongst your members by providing safety protocols like regular temperature checks, sanitisers, along with socially distant workstations and signages that guide their movement within the space.</p>



<p>For example, setting up a task force that is accessible 24&#215;7, is updated with government protocols and has access to medical assistance in times of emergencies, shows that you are there to support them no matter what.</p>



<p>Designing more spacious workspaces, including more natural light, plants and open-air spaces can make the work environment more comfortable as well as an attractive place to work out of. Creating service offerings that benefit your members and offer flexibility along with easy access to the workspace and its amenities allows them to design their work strategies effectively.</p>



<h3>Tailor-made solutions</h3>



<p>As a co-working space, you have the skill as well as access to resources that can prove extremely beneficial and crucial in times when the members themselves need to focus on business continuity.</p>



<ol><li>Providing a platform for collaboration<br>Knowing that you are not alone in these difficult times and have a community that is dealing with similar challenges can help reduce stress and loneliness. You can create a virtual platform using the available online software and tools to allow members to post their questions and concerns. The key here is to keep it active and consistent. You can start by initiating certain conversations that can help build momentum.</li></ol>



<ol start="2"><li>Virtual marketplace for their services<br>In a period of business uncertainty, you can encourage your member community to talk about their services and exchange skill sets to tap into an existing business network that your co-working space hosts.</li></ol>



<ol start="3"><li>Partnerships to access services<br>Designing partnerships that are attuned to the business needs of your members will help them access resources and build their business with much more ease. For example, a packaged solution to launch an ecommerce platform to take your business online or affordable digital marketing solutions is something that will help take off the load.</li></ol>



<ol start="4"><li>Curating member experiences virtually<br>When a business chooses to work out of a coworking space, it is also looking for something more than an office space as well. It’s imperative for the team to ensure that it’s not just a desk but a team of highly-skilled professionals who are at work to ensure the community thrives and flourishes.</li></ol>



<ul><li>Offer subscriptions to online productivity-based or earning and development apps.</li><li>When working from home or having to manage a team remotely, discounts and offers for various video conferencing tools, home office products etc can prove beneficial.</li><li>Curating webinars, workshops, fun entertaining virtual workout sessions, games or potlucks can bring the community together. At the same time, curating talks by industry experts, discussions on topics that matter like sustainability or industry trends help add value to the member community.</li></ul>



<h3>Involve and be present</h3>



<p><br>Beyond brands, members are also tangible and more localised evidence of the way the industries are adapting and sustaining in the new reality.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s important to include them in your planning, talk to them about strategies and offerings that will benefit and help them get through these uncertain times.</p>



<p>For example, reach out to the HR heads of each company and understand the business and employee status and see what gaps can be filled by you, understand what lateral support can be provided not just to the business but also to individual employees, you never know how one man&#8217;s need becomes a potential value add for the entire community</p>



<p>After a harrowing year, employees want to be a part of something where they belong. Check their well being, remember important days, and be proactive in celebrating them with them, always be prompt in responding to their queries and requests. As a way of subtle conversation or via structured methods, always seek feedback as it will help you design better experiences that align with their needs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/workspace/how-co-working-spaces-can-maintain-community-spirit-in-the-new-normal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of the Office is Productivity-as-a-Service</title>
		<link>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/working-space/the-future-of-the-office-is-productivity-as-a-service/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/working-space/the-future-of-the-office-is-productivity-as-a-service/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 04:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Working Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workspace]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The workplace has been evolving quickly over the last few years, with everyone trying to convince the world they know what the new way of working will look like. These...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The workplace has been evolving quickly over the last few years, with everyone trying to convince the world they know what the new way of working will look like. These same people try to paint the new work world order black and white, saying the office of the future is a choice between work from home versus work from the office, activity-based working versus traditional workstations, or flexible versus long-term leases.</p>



<p>As with any complicated decision, the choice is rarely binary. The reality is the workplace of the future is that it will be a combination of all of these things. No matter what the office of the future looks and feels like there is still one metric that is important above all others: productivity.</p>



<p>People dismiss the idea of productivity as an important KPI for office space. They usually say that productivity is too hard to “measure.” Productivity is often looked at as an intangible, but that doesn’t mean you can’t understand its impact in a meaningful, quantitative way.</p>



<p>First, let’s create a formula to understand our framework. If the outcome we are aiming for is productivity, then what we really want to do is increase output. Let’s define output in this case as creativity by revenue. Obviously, output isn’t everything. If output goes up but it takes longer to produce it, you have not changed productivity. So what we are really talking about is efficiency which is, at its most basic level, is cost over time. That means that (CxR)x (C/T)=P. Or, to simplify productivity equals output times efficiency, P=Output x Effieciency</p>



<p>If the landlords can find ways to optimize this equation in a verifiable way then both tenants and LPs will seek these landlords out above all others. The low hanging fruit for landlords to help increase efficiency is by automating mundane tasks associated with interacting with the workplace. This can include room or desk booking, access control, and billing. It might seem that shortening these often uncomplicated tasks wouldn’t move the needle but remember that if you multiply this every day for every employee it really does help boost efficiency in a meaningful way.</p>



<p>Output can be increased by an office as well. By enabling collaboration, engagement, wellness, and support, offices can boost both the creativity and the revenue associated with output. Data that offices collect can help companies better use their resources and make a palpable impact on output.</p>



<p>While the pandemic has clearly accelerated people’s push for remote work, the overwhelming consensus seems to be that companies and workplaces will resort to a hybrid model of in-person and remote work. The driver for this hybrid model for organizations will be what creates the most productive output for my organization and what tools do I have to engage my workforce to reach this outcome?</p>



<p>The question for landlords is whether this switch in the way we work is an opportunity or a threat. The change was already underway when many co working providers proved the need for flexibility around commercial leasing. And even though some of co working providers execution was poor, that need is still alive and well, albeit sheltering at home for now.</p>



<p>It is important to remember that landlords now have the opportunity to move from selling “four walls,” which will almost certainly be in less demand, to selling productivity. The demand for productivity is robust, inelastic and recession proof. By switching their thinking about what they are actually selling, landlords will be able to capitalize on the community that they have built, provide an unlimited amount of related services for their customers and ultimately create networks that enable the occupants of that built environment the flexibility that they have become accustomed to.</p>



<p>The built environment is still a cornerstone of productivity for many organizations. The need to collaborate, the ability to onboard and train new employees, the creation of company culture, and the vicarious interactions that create so many productive outputs will always be a critical foundation for any organization. Productivity tools are the glue that binds organizations. To put it differently, the workspace is the “Sun” which the workplace “system” revolves around.</p>



<p>Again, we are taking a broad view of what a workplace is. It includes office space, plus frictionless, self service flexible work options, remote productivity tools, network access, perks, amenities, health and wellness and an array of data to compliment all of this.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thirdhome.space/en/working-space/the-future-of-the-office-is-productivity-as-a-service/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
