<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Working Space &#8211; Loyagami Indonesia | Real Estate Asset &amp; Investment Management Platform</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.loyagami.com/en/category/working-space/feed/?simply_static_page=1750" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.loyagami.com/</link>
	<description>Makes property-based investment and asset management easier</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 15:57:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>Powered by Teleciuos?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How co-working spaces can maintain community spirit in the new normal</title>
		<link>https://www.loyagami.com/en/workspace/how-co-working-spaces-can-maintain-community-spirit-in-the-new-normal/</link>
					<comments>https://www.loyagami.com/en/workspace/how-co-working-spaces-can-maintain-community-spirit-in-the-new-normal/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 05:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Workspace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Space]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3718</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The current pandemic conditions have changed many ways of working, especially the expectations of workers to work in a co-working space]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p>Few things that we do to keep people engaged in shared workspace </p></blockquote>



<p>The pandemic has challenged our society and fundamentally upended its social construct. While its impact may last long with social distancing, lockdowns, and resulting economic fallout becoming the new norms, we do have the resilience to pull through these tough times.</p>



<p>Since the ease of lockdown restrictions last year, a lot of efforts have been made to ensure re-entry, return to work, and reopening of businesses and institutions. But now with the second wave of the pandemic hitting us hard, it looks all the more difficult.</p>



<p>While several industries are trying to adapt and thrive in this economic downturn there is a need for innovation, flexibility and agility in the way we operate. This has become a reality for the co-working industry in particular, as they are forced to reassess their operations, offer flexible membership plans, and introduce new business models. While adapting to accommodate the hybrid model of working and de-densifying demands of the businesses would benefit the sector in the long run, how does one ensure retention?</p>



<p>Community engagement has always been a strategy that has led to retention but it is a challenge when spaces are not allowed to bring a sizable number of people together. Here are some strategies that can assist in ensuring that you retain an engaged community despite the odds:</p>



<h3>Communicate with your community</h3>



<p>The most important thing to do is keep a consistent and open line of communication with your community at all times. Address their safety concerns by communicating the precautionary measures incorporated by your workspace. Instil a sense of confidence amongst your members by providing safety protocols like regular temperature checks, sanitisers, along with socially distant workstations and signages that guide their movement within the space.</p>



<p>For example, setting up a task force that is accessible 24&#215;7, is updated with government protocols and has access to medical assistance in times of emergencies, shows that you are there to support them no matter what.</p>



<p>Designing more spacious workspaces, including more natural light, plants and open-air spaces can make the work environment more comfortable as well as an attractive place to work out of. Creating service offerings that benefit your members and offer flexibility along with easy access to the workspace and its amenities allows them to design their work strategies effectively.</p>



<h3>Tailor-made solutions</h3>



<p>As a co-working space, you have the skill as well as access to resources that can prove extremely beneficial and crucial in times when the members themselves need to focus on business continuity.</p>



<ol><li>Providing a platform for collaboration<br>Knowing that you are not alone in these difficult times and have a community that is dealing with similar challenges can help reduce stress and loneliness. You can create a virtual platform using the available online software and tools to allow members to post their questions and concerns. The key here is to keep it active and consistent. You can start by initiating certain conversations that can help build momentum.</li></ol>



<ol start="2"><li>Virtual marketplace for their services<br>In a period of business uncertainty, you can encourage your member community to talk about their services and exchange skill sets to tap into an existing business network that your co-working space hosts.</li></ol>



<ol start="3"><li>Partnerships to access services<br>Designing partnerships that are attuned to the business needs of your members will help them access resources and build their business with much more ease. For example, a packaged solution to launch an ecommerce platform to take your business online or affordable digital marketing solutions is something that will help take off the load.</li></ol>



<ol start="4"><li>Curating member experiences virtually<br>When a business chooses to work out of a coworking space, it is also looking for something more than an office space as well. It’s imperative for the team to ensure that it’s not just a desk but a team of highly-skilled professionals who are at work to ensure the community thrives and flourishes.</li></ol>



<ul><li>Offer subscriptions to online productivity-based or earning and development apps.</li><li>When working from home or having to manage a team remotely, discounts and offers for various video conferencing tools, home office products etc can prove beneficial.</li><li>Curating webinars, workshops, fun entertaining virtual workout sessions, games or potlucks can bring the community together. At the same time, curating talks by industry experts, discussions on topics that matter like sustainability or industry trends help add value to the member community.</li></ul>



<h3>Involve and be present</h3>



<p><br>Beyond brands, members are also tangible and more localised evidence of the way the industries are adapting and sustaining in the new reality.</p>



<p>It&#8217;s important to include them in your planning, talk to them about strategies and offerings that will benefit and help them get through these uncertain times.</p>



<p>For example, reach out to the HR heads of each company and understand the business and employee status and see what gaps can be filled by you, understand what lateral support can be provided not just to the business but also to individual employees, you never know how one man&#8217;s need becomes a potential value add for the entire community</p>



<p>After a harrowing year, employees want to be a part of something where they belong. Check their well being, remember important days, and be proactive in celebrating them with them, always be prompt in responding to their queries and requests. As a way of subtle conversation or via structured methods, always seek feedback as it will help you design better experiences that align with their needs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.loyagami.com/en/workspace/how-co-working-spaces-can-maintain-community-spirit-in-the-new-normal/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of the Office is Productivity-as-a-Service</title>
		<link>https://www.loyagami.com/en/working-space/the-future-of-the-office-is-productivity-as-a-service/</link>
					<comments>https://www.loyagami.com/en/working-space/the-future-of-the-office-is-productivity-as-a-service/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[firmans]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 04:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Working Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Workspace]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.loyagami.com/?p=3069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The workplace has been evolving quickly over the last few years, with everyone trying to convince the world they know what the new way of working will look like. These...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The workplace has been evolving quickly over the last few years, with everyone trying to convince the world they know what the new way of working will look like. These same people try to paint the new work world order black and white, saying the office of the future is a choice between work from home versus work from the office, activity-based working versus traditional workstations, or flexible versus long-term leases.</p>



<p>As with any complicated decision, the choice is rarely binary. The reality is the workplace of the future is that it will be a combination of all of these things. No matter what the office of the future looks and feels like there is still one metric that is important above all others: productivity.</p>



<p>People dismiss the idea of productivity as an important KPI for office space. They usually say that productivity is too hard to “measure.” Productivity is often looked at as an intangible, but that doesn’t mean you can’t understand its impact in a meaningful, quantitative way.</p>



<p>First, let’s create a formula to understand our framework. If the outcome we are aiming for is productivity, then what we really want to do is increase output. Let’s define output in this case as creativity by revenue. Obviously, output isn’t everything. If output goes up but it takes longer to produce it, you have not changed productivity. So what we are really talking about is efficiency which is, at its most basic level, is cost over time. That means that (CxR)x (C/T)=P. Or, to simplify productivity equals output times efficiency, P=Output x Effieciency</p>



<p>If the landlords can find ways to optimize this equation in a verifiable way then both tenants and LPs will seek these landlords out above all others. The low hanging fruit for landlords to help increase efficiency is by automating mundane tasks associated with interacting with the workplace. This can include room or desk booking, access control, and billing. It might seem that shortening these often uncomplicated tasks wouldn’t move the needle but remember that if you multiply this every day for every employee it really does help boost efficiency in a meaningful way.</p>



<p>Output can be increased by an office as well. By enabling collaboration, engagement, wellness, and support, offices can boost both the creativity and the revenue associated with output. Data that offices collect can help companies better use their resources and make a palpable impact on output.</p>



<p>While the pandemic has clearly accelerated people’s push for remote work, the overwhelming consensus seems to be that companies and workplaces will resort to a hybrid model of in-person and remote work. The driver for this hybrid model for organizations will be what creates the most productive output for my organization and what tools do I have to engage my workforce to reach this outcome?</p>



<p>The question for landlords is whether this switch in the way we work is an opportunity or a threat. The change was already underway when many co working providers proved the need for flexibility around commercial leasing. And even though some of co working providers execution was poor, that need is still alive and well, albeit sheltering at home for now.</p>



<p>It is important to remember that landlords now have the opportunity to move from selling “four walls,” which will almost certainly be in less demand, to selling productivity. The demand for productivity is robust, inelastic and recession proof. By switching their thinking about what they are actually selling, landlords will be able to capitalize on the community that they have built, provide an unlimited amount of related services for their customers and ultimately create networks that enable the occupants of that built environment the flexibility that they have become accustomed to.</p>



<p>The built environment is still a cornerstone of productivity for many organizations. The need to collaborate, the ability to onboard and train new employees, the creation of company culture, and the vicarious interactions that create so many productive outputs will always be a critical foundation for any organization. Productivity tools are the glue that binds organizations. To put it differently, the workspace is the “Sun” which the workplace “system” revolves around.</p>



<p>Again, we are taking a broad view of what a workplace is. It includes office space, plus frictionless, self service flexible work options, remote productivity tools, network access, perks, amenities, health and wellness and an array of data to compliment all of this.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.loyagami.com/en/working-space/the-future-of-the-office-is-productivity-as-a-service/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
